http://www.merlin-os.co.uk/doc/privacy.html

Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to us. We only use your information as shown in this policy, and never pass your information to third parties unless required to by law.
Tweet
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy sets out how Merlin Open Systems uses and protects any information that you give Merlin Open Systems when you use this web site.
Merlin Open Systems is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this web site, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
Merlin Open Systems may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 1st February 2006.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
name and job title
contact information including e-mail address
demographic information such as post code, preferences and interests
other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional e-mail about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the e-mail address which you have provided.
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by e-mail, phone or mail.
We may use the information to customise the web site according to your interests.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
Cookies
We use cookies on this site for two purposes only:
To track the contents of your shopping basket, which is handled by PayPal Business.
To remember your location (region or country, and VAT number where applicable) so that we can calculate VAT (value added tax) appropriately.
Links to other web sites
Our web site may contain links to enable you to visit other web sites of interest easily. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other web site. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the web site in question.
Controlling your personal information
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we are required by law. We will not use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to Merlin Open Systems. We can also be contacted by e-mail at info @ merlin-os.co.uk.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to us or e-mail us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
Copyright © Merlin Open Systems 1997–2020
